<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<ResearchProjectDef>
	<defName>WTH_HackingBasics</defName>
	<label>mechanoid hacking basics</label>
	<tab>WTH_ResearchTab</tab>
	<techLevel>Spacer</techLevel>
	<description>Learn the basics of hacking. Gives access to the hacking table and the mechanoid platform. The hacking table can be used to hack into the targeting system of mechanoids, making sure they attack your enemy instead of you when activated. Also allows you to build mechanoid platforms, which are  needed as a maintenance and as a power station for mechanoids.</description>
	<baseCost>1000</baseCost>
	<prerequisites>
	  <li>MicroelectronicsBasics</li>
	</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>0</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>0</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef>
	<defName>WTH_HackingRemoteControl</defName>
	<label>hacking and controlling locomotion systems</label>
	<tab>WTH_ResearchTab</tab>
	<techLevel>Spacer</techLevel>
	<description>Learn how to hack the locomotion system of hacked mechanoids and how to control them with colonists using a remote controlling belt which can be crafted at the machining table. Finally your non-violent colonists can participate in battle without feeling guilty by taking control over your mechanoid palls. After all, it's the mechanoids doing the killing, not them, right?</description>
	<baseCost>1600</baseCost>
	<prerequisites>
	  <li>WTH_HackingBasics</li>
	</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>1</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>1</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<ResearchProjectDef>
	<defName>WTH_PortableChemfuelPlatform</defName>
	<label>Portable chemfuel charging platform</label>
	<tab>WTH_ResearchTab</tab>
	<techLevel>Spacer</techLevel>
	<description>Allows the creation of portable chemfuel powered platforms, which supply your mechanoids with power while they explore the world. Can also be installed/uninstalled for a temporary power solution for your mechanoids.</description>
	<baseCost>500</baseCost>
	<prerequisites>
	  <li>BiofuelRefining</li>
	  <li>WTH_HackingBasics</li>
	</prerequisites>
	<researchViewX>1</researchViewX>
	<researchViewY>2</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<ResearchProjectDef>
	<defName>WTH_HackingAdvanced</defName>
	<label>AI implanting</label>
	<tab>WTH_ResearchTab</tab>
	<techLevel>Spacer</techLevel>
	<description>Research the possibility to implant AI Persona Cores in hacked mechanoids, giving full control over them for combat purposes.</description>
	<baseCost>2400</baseCost>
	<prerequisites>
	  <li>MicroelectronicsBasics</li>
	  <li>WTH_HackingBasics</li>
	</prerequisites>
	<researchViewX>2</researchViewX>
	<researchViewY>0</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	

	
</Defs>