<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="UpdateFeatureBase_WhatTheHack">
		<modNameReadable>What the Hack!?</modNameReadable>
		<modIdentifier>WhatTheHack</modIdentifier>
		<linkUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1505914869</linkUrl>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_WhatTheHack">
		<defName>WhatTheHack_2_1_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.1.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
What the Hack has been updated to support Rimworld 1.1. Many thanks go to Ogliss and SargBjornson for helping out with updating, and to anyone who helped testing. 

Update notes:
- Compatibility with Rimworld 1.1. (Rimworld 1.0 is still supported)
- Reworked world events so they use the new quest system. 
- Fixed some issues with hediff descriptions
- Rebalanced rogue AI: decreased mood cost of various abilities and shortened cooldowns. 
- Minor balance tweaks. 
- Compatibility with Save our Ship 2. 
- Compatibility with Animals Logic. 

What the hack should still support any mechanoid, modded or not. This includes the new Pikeman mechanoid. If you do happen to find any issues, Please report them. Don't forget to include a HugsLib log. Press ctrl+f12 after the issue occurs, or press the green share log button to get a shareable link.
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_WhatTheHack">
		<defName>WhatTheHack_2_1_5</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>2.1.5</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
What the Hack is updated to version 2.1.5
		
Update notes:
- Fixed mechanoids not having a "work mode" button after installing a work module.
&lt;color=orange&gt;&lt;b&gt;IMPORTANT NOTE: if you currently have mechanoids with work modules installed that lack the work mode button, just uninstall and then re-install the module, that should fix it. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt; 

Changelog for previous recent updates:

v2.1.4: 
- Big performance improvement.
- Fixed conflict with Save our Ship 2 related to recipes being added to mechs.

v2.1.3
- Rimworld 1.1.2609 compatibility.

v2.1.2
- Fixed incorrect maintenance threshold (was introduced last update).

v2.1.1
- Fixed various performance issues. What the Hack should run much more smoothly now. This wouldn't have been possible without Dubs Performance Analyzer, so thumbs up to him.
- Fixed not being able to uninstall upgrade modules.

	</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_WhatTheHack">
		<defName>WhatTheHack_3_0_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>3.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
What the Hack is updated to support Rimworld 1.2. Moreover, this update comes with a bunch of fixes that also work for v1.1: 
- Fixed caravanning with mechs breaking the needs of pawns in the caravan.
- Fixed problem with assigning mechs to caravans. 
- Fixed glitched meteorites with mech parts showing up. 
- Renamed the long range mineral scanner tuning research to hive data tracking so people will hopefully understand how to get Hive data. 

Credits go to NoirFry for helping out solving some of the issues. 

I also updated Giddy-up! Mechanoids to support Rimworld 1.2, so you can also Ride your mechs to battle!

If you run into any issues, please report them with a hugslib log (press ctrl+f12 in-game to get one). Enjoy the update!
Cheers,
Roolo
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
		<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_WhatTheHack">
		<defName>WhatTheHack_4_0_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>4.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
What the Hack is updated to support Rimworld 1.3. Along with all the fixes that needed to be done to make it work for 1.3, this update comes with a the following changes: 
- Mechanoid parts should no long appear in meteorites (with a broken texture)
- Mechanoids get the option to hunt. Check out the mechanoids tab for toggling the hunting work priority (or for disabling it).
Turn on work mode to allow the mech to hunt. 

&lt;color=orange&gt;&lt;b&gt;Many credits go to Ogliss for doing a major part of this update.**&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;

If you run into any issues, please report them with a hugslib log (press ctrl+f12 in-game to get one). 

As you might know I'm not really active as modder anymore, but I do intend to keep all my mods alive. The reason I'm no longer active is because I'm working on my own game: &lt;color=orange&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cursed Crew&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;. If you like my work, be sure to check it out! You can find a link to Cursed Crew the mod page of every mod I created. 

Enjoy the update!

Cheers,
Roolo
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="UpdateFeatureBase_WhatTheHack">
		<defName>WhatTheHack_5_0_0</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>5.0.0</assemblyVersion>
		<content>
What the Hack is updated to support Rimworld 1.4. This update comes with a couple of performance improvements as well.  
&lt;color=orange&gt;&lt;b&gt;Many thanks go to Mlie who did this update completely. **&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;

Rimworld 1.4 came with a ton of mechanoid related changes, and it wasn't feasible for us to test every single interaction with this mod. So please beware that there could be issues. I you encounter any, please report them with a hugslib log (press ctrl+f12 in-game to get one).
Enjoy the update!

Cheers,
Roolo
		</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
</Defs>