<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>
	<WTH_Letter_Success_Label>Hacking successful</WTH_Letter_Success_Label>
	<WTH_Letter_Success_Label_Description>{0} has successfully hacked a mechanoid and named it {1}. Targeting system of {1} now targets your enemies instead of your pawns. However, to avoid detection by the Mechanoid Hive, {1} has to rely on its internal backup batteries.</WTH_Letter_Success_Label_Description>
	<WTH_Letter_Nothing_Label>Hacking failed - just some damage</WTH_Letter_Nothing_Label>
	<WTH_Letter_Nothing_Description>Hacking failed, but apart from some damage to the mechanoid nothing serious happened</WTH_Letter_Nothing_Description>
	<WTH_Letter_HackedPoorly_Label>Hacking barely succeeded</WTH_Letter_HackedPoorly_Label>
	<WTH_Letter_HackedPoorly_Description>While the mechanoid is hacked for now, the job isn't done well. Use this mechanoid at your own risk, or discard it</WTH_Letter_HackedPoorly_Description>
	<WTH_Letter_CausedMechanoidRaid_Label>Hacking failed - emergency signal transmitted</WTH_Letter_CausedMechanoidRaid_Label>
	<WTH_Letter_CausedMechanoidRaid_Description>One of your colonists somehow managed to activate a security mechanism that broadcasted a signal to nearby mechanoids. Prepare for more flesh machines...</WTH_Letter_CausedMechanoidRaid_Description>
	<WTH_Letter_ShotRandomDirection_Label>Hacking failed - whoops</WTH_Letter_ShotRandomDirection_Label>
	<WTH_Letter_ShotRandomDirection_Description>One of your colonists accidentally triggered the mechanoids main weapon. Whoops.</WTH_Letter_ShotRandomDirection_Description>
	<WTH_Letter_HealedToStanding_Label>Hacking failed - mechanoid standing again</WTH_Letter_HealedToStanding_Label>
	<WTH_Letter_HealedToStanding_Description>The mechanoid wasn't really disabled after all, while being hacked, it managed to recover and it is now a danger to your colony.</WTH_Letter_HealedToStanding_Description>
	<WTH_Letter_Mech_Reverted_Label>Hack stopped working</WTH_Letter_Mech_Reverted_Label>
	<WTH_Letter_Mech_Reverted_Description>A mechanoid that was poorly maintained reverted to its original deadly behaviour.</WTH_Letter_Mech_Reverted_Description>
	<WTH_Letter_HackedPoorlyEvent_Label>Something snapped</WTH_Letter_HackedPoorlyEvent_Label>
	<WTH_Letter_HackedPoorlyEvent_Description>Something snapped in the head of a mechanoid that was hacked poorly. Urgent maintenance is needed.</WTH_Letter_HackedPoorlyEvent_Description>
	<WTH_FailureChance_Nothing_Title>Failure chance: nothing happens</WTH_FailureChance_Nothing_Title>
	<WTH_FailureChance_Nothing_Description>Chance that nothing escalates when hacking fails</WTH_FailureChance_Nothing_Description>
	<WTH_FailureChance_CauseRaid_Title>Failure chance: cause raid</WTH_FailureChance_CauseRaid_Title>
	<WTH_FailureChance_CauseRaid_Description>Chance that a raid is caused when hacking fails</WTH_FailureChance_CauseRaid_Description>
	<WTH_FailureChance_ShootRandomDirection_Title>Failure chance: weapon fire</WTH_FailureChance_ShootRandomDirection_Title>	
	<WTH_FailureChance_ShootRandomDirection_Description>Chance a mechanoid's main weapons fires in a random direction when hacking fails</WTH_FailureChance_ShootRandomDirection_Description>
	<WTH_FailureChance_HealToStanding_Title>Failure chance: heal to standing</WTH_FailureChance_HealToStanding_Title>
	<WTH_FailureChance_HealToStanding_Description>Chance a mechanoid is healed until it can stand when hacking fails</WTH_FailureChance_HealToStanding_Description>
	<WTH_FailureChance_HackPoorly_Title>Failure chance: hacked poorly</WTH_FailureChance_HackPoorly_Title>
	<WTH_FailureChance_HackPoorly_Description>Chance a mechanoid is hacked poorly when hacking fails</WTH_FailureChance_HackPoorly_Description>
	<WTH_MaintenanceDedayEnabled_Title>Maintenance decay enabled</WTH_MaintenanceDedayEnabled_Title>
	<WTH_MaintenanceDedayEnabled_Description>Uncheck this if you don't want to regularly maintain your mechanoids. With this unchecked, the maintenance need bar will still be shown, but it won't decrease over time. There are still certain events that can deplete the maintenance bar of mechanoids.</WTH_MaintenanceDedayEnabled_Description>
	
	<!--BEGIN: added in v0.19.6 -->
	<WTH_TextMote_OperationFailed>Operation failed (success chance: {0})</WTH_TextMote_OperationFailed>
	<WTH_Letter_CausedIntendedMechanoidRaid_Label>Emergency signal successfully transmitted</WTH_Letter_CausedIntendedMechanoidRaid_Label>
	<WTH_Letter_CausedIntendedMechanoidRaid_Description>Your hacker succeeded in intentionally letting a mechanoid transmit an emergency signal, but he damaged the mechanoid in the process. Was it a good idea though?</WTH_Letter_CausedIntendedMechanoidRaid_Description>
	<WTH_Letter_CausedIntendedMechanoidRaidTooLarge_Label>Emergency signal too powerful</WTH_Letter_CausedIntendedMechanoidRaidTooLarge_Label>
	<WTH_Letter_CausedIntendedMechanoidRaidTooLarge_Description>After your hacker fiddled around with the mechanism capable of emitting signals a deafening loud shriek emerged from the mechanoid. Due to the incompetence of your hacker to predict this outcome, the transmitted emergency signal was much more strong than anticipated. Prepare for the worst.</WTH_Letter_CausedIntendedMechanoidRaidTooLarge_Description>
	<WTH_Expand>Expand</WTH_Expand>
	<WTH_Collapse>Collapse</WTH_Collapse>
	<WTH_SettingsGroup_Raids_Title>Raid settings</WTH_SettingsGroup_Raids_Title>
	<WTH_SettingsGroup_Raids_Description>Configure the mechanoid usage chance for enemy raids.</WTH_SettingsGroup_Raids_Description>
	<WTH_SettingsGroup_HackFailure_Title>Hacking failure settings (contains spoilers)</WTH_SettingsGroup_HackFailure_Title>
	<WTH_SettingsGroup_HackFailure_Description>Configure the chances of different events that can occur when hacking fails. The chances are normalised in case they don't add up to 100.</WTH_SettingsGroup_HackFailure_Description>
	<WTH_FailureChance_IntRaidTooLarge_Title>Failure chance: cause big raid</WTH_FailureChance_IntRaidTooLarge_Title>
	<WTH_FailureChance_IntRaidTooLarge_Description>The chance that a much too strong emergency signal is emitted when a pawn tries to deliberately trigger an emergency signal. Note: this event can not occur during regular hacking.</WTH_FailureChance_IntRaidTooLarge_Description>
	<WTH_SettingsGroup_Balance_Title>Balance altering settings</WTH_SettingsGroup_Balance_Title>
	<WTH_SettingsGroup_Balance_Description>These settings have a high impact on how balanced the mod is. You can tweak them to suit your needs, but it's recommended to first try the mod on default settings for the intended experience. If you think the defaults aren't reasonable, please report this on the workshop or forum page of this mod.</WTH_SettingsGroup_Balance_Description>	
	<WTH_MaintenanceDedayModifier_Title>Maintenance decay modifier</WTH_MaintenanceDedayModifier_Title>
	<WTH_MaintenanceDedayModifier_Description>Modify the maintenance decay rate with this option. Example: setting this to 0.5 would result in maintenance decaying twice as slow.</WTH_MaintenanceDedayModifier_Description>
	<WTH_RepairConsumptionModifier_Title>Repair part consumption modifier</WTH_RepairConsumptionModifier_Title>
	<WTH_RepairConsumptionModifier_Description>Modify the amount of parts required for repairing your mechs (on platforms or with upgrade modules). Example: setting this to 0.5 would make repairing twice as cheap.</WTH_RepairConsumptionModifier_Description>
	<WTH_PartDropRateModifier_Title>Part drop rate modifier</WTH_PartDropRateModifier_Title>
	<WTH_PartDropRateModifier_Description>Modify the drop rate of mechanoid parts. Example: setting this to 2.0 would result in twice the amount of parts being dropped when a mechanoid is disassembled.</WTH_PartDropRateModifier_Description>
	<WTH_ChipDropRateModifier_Title>Chip drop rate modifier</WTH_ChipDropRateModifier_Title>
	<WTH_ChipDropRateModifier_Description>Modify the drop rate of advanced mechanoid chips. Example: setting this to 2.0 would result in twice the amount of chips being dropped when a mechanoid is disassembled.</WTH_ChipDropRateModifier_Description>
	<WTH_PowerFallModifier_Title>Power fall modifier</WTH_PowerFallModifier_Title>
	<WTH_PowerFallModifier_Description>Modify how quickly mechanoids drain power from their batteries. Example: setting this to 0.5 would result in the power dropping twice as slowly.</WTH_PowerFallModifier_Description>
	<WTH_PowerChargeModifier_Title>Power charge modifier </WTH_PowerChargeModifier_Title>
	<WTH_PowerChargeModifier_Description>Modify how quickly mechanoids charge their batteries. Example: setting this to 2.0 would result in the power charging twice as fast.</WTH_PowerChargeModifier_Description>
	<!--END: added in v0.19.6 -->
	
	
	
	<WTH_HackedMechChance_Title>Chance enemies use hacked mechs (%)</WTH_HackedMechChance_Title>
	<WTH_HackedMechChance_Description>The chance that factions allowed in the mod options use hacked mechanoids when raiding your base.</WTH_HackedMechChance_Description>
	<WTH_MaxHackedMechPoints_Title>Maximum extra points for hacked mechs (%)</WTH_MaxHackedMechPoints_Title>
	<WTH_MaxHackedMechPoints_Description>This determines the point budget for spawning hacked enemy mechanoids. If an enemy raid spawns with hacked mechanoids, a random number between the minimum hacked points setting and this setting determines how much % of the raid points will be available for spawning mechanoids. Example: If a raid has a point budget of 1000, this setting is set to 50%, and the minimum set to 20%, 200 to 500 points worth of hacked mechanoids will spawn in addition to the original raid. </WTH_MaxHackedMechPoints_Description>
	<WTH_MinHackedMechPoints_Title>Minimum extra points for hacked mechs (%)</WTH_MinHackedMechPoints_Title>
	<WTH_MinHackedMechPoints_Description>This determines the point budget for spawning hacked enemy mechanoids. If an enemy raid spawns with hacked mechanoids, a random number between this setting and the maximum hacking points setting determines how much % of the raid points will be available for spawning mechanoids. Example :If a raid has a point budget of 1000, the maximum is set to 50% and this setting is set to 20%, 200 to 500 points worth of hacked mechanoids will spawn in addition to the original raid. </WTH_MinHackedMechPoints_Description>
	
	<WTH_Menu_ClearTable>Clear hacking table</WTH_Menu_ClearTable>
	
	<WTH_Reason_NotOnTable>Not on functioning hacking facility</WTH_Reason_NotOnTable>	
	<WTH_Reason_MechanoidDowned>Cannot enable downed mechanoid</WTH_Reason_MechanoidDowned>
	<WTH_Reason_PowerLow>Cannot enable mechanoid, power too low (disable auto-recharge to override this)</WTH_Reason_PowerLow>
	<WTH_Reason_PawnCannotBeDrafted>Cannot enable operate mechanoid controller belt when drafted</WTH_Reason_PawnCannotBeDrafted>
	
	<WTH_Gizmo_SearchAndDestroy_Label>Activate</WTH_Gizmo_SearchAndDestroy_Label>
	<WTH_Gizmo_SearchAndDestroy_Description>Activate the mechanoid. It will automatically attack any enemies near your colony. When disabled, the mechanoid will return to a mechanoid platform when possible.</WTH_Gizmo_SearchAndDestroy_Description>
	<WTH_Gizmo_AutoRecharge_Label>Auto recharge</WTH_Gizmo_AutoRecharge_Label>
	<WTH_Gizmo_AutoRecharge_Description>With this mode enabled, mechanoids automatically go back to a mechanoid platform when they are running low on power.</WTH_Gizmo_AutoRecharge_Description>
	
	<WTH_Gizmo_RemoteControlActivate_Label>Activate</WTH_Gizmo_RemoteControlActivate_Label>
	<WTH_Gizmo_RemoteControlActivate_Description>Use the mechanoid controller belt to control a mechanoid directly</WTH_Gizmo_RemoteControlActivate_Description>
	<WTH_Gizmo_RemoteControlDeactivate_Label>Deactivate</WTH_Gizmo_RemoteControlDeactivate_Label>
	<WTH_Gizmo_RemoteControlDeactivate_Description>Deactivates mechanoid controller belt, giving control back to the mechanoid</WTH_Gizmo_RemoteControlDeactivate_Description>
	
	<WTH_Gizmo_Regenerate_Label>Regenerate body parts</WTH_Gizmo_Regenerate_Label>
	<WTH_Gizmo_Regenerate_Description>When this is active, the platform regenerates body parts of the mechanoid that are missing. Regenerating body parts consumes a maximum {0} mechanoid parts for each body part (small body parts require less). Parts only start to regenerate when the mech has no other damage</WTH_Gizmo_Regenerate_Description>
	<WTH_Gizmo_Repair_Label>Repair mechanoid</WTH_Gizmo_Repair_Label>
	<WTH_Gizmo_Repair_Description>When this is active, the platform repairs any mechanoid on the platform by activating its internal mechanites by providing enough power, and material to work with. The mechanites consume mechanoid parts stored in the platform in the process.</WTH_Gizmo_Repair_Description>

	<WTH_Gizmo_SelfDestruct_Label>Self destruct</WTH_Gizmo_SelfDestruct_Label>
	<WTH_Gizmo_SelfDestruct_Description>Let the mechanoid go with a bang.</WTH_Gizmo_SelfDestruct_Description>
	
	<WTH_Gizmo_Mech_Repair_Label>Repair</WTH_Gizmo_Mech_Repair_Label>
	<WTH_Gizmo_Mech_Repair_Description>Orders the mechanoid to use its repair arm to transfer mechanites charged by the repair module to other mechs, repairing them.</WTH_Gizmo_Mech_Repair_Description>
	<WTH_Gizmo_SelfRepair_Label>Self repair</WTH_Gizmo_SelfRepair_Label>
	<WTH_Gizmo_SelfRepair_Description>Orders the mechanoid to activate the repair module, which causes surge of energy, activating the mechanoid's internal mechanites. These start to repair immediately using the parts stored in the module.</WTH_Gizmo_SelfRepair_Description>
	
	<WTH_Gizmo_Mech_EquipBelt_Label>Equip belt</WTH_Gizmo_Mech_EquipBelt_Label>
	<WTH_Gizmo_Mech_EquipBelt_Description>Orders the mech to use its belt module to equip any type of belt normally used by humanoids.</WTH_Gizmo_Mech_EquipBelt_Description>
	
	<WTH_Reason_AlreadyRepairing>This mechanoid is already injected with charged repairing mechanoids.</WTH_Reason_AlreadyRepairing>
	<WTH_Reason_NeedsMorePower>At least {0} power is needed to activate this.</WTH_Reason_NeedsMorePower>
	<WTH_Reason_NeedsMoreFuel>At least {0} fuel is needed to activate this.</WTH_Reason_NeedsMoreFuel>
	<WTH_Reason_NotActivated>This cannot be used with a deactivated mechanoid.</WTH_Reason_NotActivated>
	<WTH_Reason_NoDamage>No damage to be repaired.</WTH_Reason_NoDamage>
	
	<WTH_Alert_EmergencySignalTransmitted_Label>Mechanoid raid imminent</WTH_Alert_EmergencySignalTransmitted_Label>
	<WTH_Alert_EmergencySignalTransmitted_Description>Mechanoids near your base are currently responding to the emergency signal that was transmitted and will arrive at your base soon.</WTH_Alert_EmergencySignalTransmitted_Description>
	<WTH_Alert_EmergencySignalCooldown_Label>Mechanoids suspicious</WTH_Alert_EmergencySignalCooldown_Label>
	<WTH_Alert_EmergencySignalCooldown_Description>Because of your recent success of drawing nearby mechanoids to your base by transmitting an emergency signal, there simply aren't many mechanoids left in the surroundings, and the ones that are left have become suspicious. You have to wait a while until new mechanoids arrive and until the suspicion wears of. This may take up to a quadrum.</WTH_Alert_EmergencySignalCooldown_Description>
	
	
	<WTH_Alert_NotEnoughPlatforms_Label>Not enough mechanoid platforms</WTH_Alert_NotEnoughPlatforms_Label>
	<WTH_Alert_NotEnoughPlatforms_Description>You have more hacked mechanoids than mechanoid platforms in your main base. Make sure to make more mechanoid platforms</WTH_Alert_NotEnoughPlatforms_Description>
	<WTH_Alert_Power_Low_Label>Mechanoids low on power</WTH_Alert_Power_Low_Label>
	<WTH_Alert_Power_Low_Description>The following mechanoids are low on power:{0}Deactivate them so they go back to a mechanoid platform</WTH_Alert_Power_Low_Description>
	<WTH_Alert_Maintenance_Low_Label>Mechanoids poorly maintained</WTH_Alert_Maintenance_Low_Label>
	<WTH_Alert_Maintenance_Low_Description>The hacked hardware of the following mechanoids is poorly maintained:{0}Make sure your hackers take a look at them.</WTH_Alert_Maintenance_Low_Description>
	<WTH_Alert_Maintenance_VeryLow_Label>Mechanoids very poorly maintained</WTH_Alert_Maintenance_VeryLow_Label>
	<WTH_Alert_Maintenance_VeryLow_Description>The hacked hardware of the following mechanoids is very poorly maintained and they pose a threat to your colony:{0}The hack can stop working at any time now, so make sure the mechanoids are either maintained, or shut down.</WTH_Alert_Maintenance_VeryLow_Description>
	<WTH_FactionRestrictions_OK>Allow</WTH_FactionRestrictions_OK>
	<WTH_FactionRestrictions_NOK>Disallow</WTH_FactionRestrictions_NOK>
	<WTH_FactionRestrictions_Label>Configure which mechanoids each faction can hack</WTH_FactionRestrictions_Label>
	<WTH_FactionRestrictions_Description>This setting allows you to configure what hacked mechanoids each faction can use during raids</WTH_FactionRestrictions_Description>
	
	<WTH_MechanoidsSection>Mechanoids</WTH_MechanoidsSection>
	
	<WTH_Explanation_BonusCapacity>Bonus capacity for this pawn type</WTH_Explanation_BonusCapacity>	
	<WTH_Explanation_NumMechs>Number of mechanoids</WTH_Explanation_NumMechs>
	<WTH_Explanation_NumPlatforms>Number of portable platforms</WTH_Explanation_NumPlatforms>
	<WTH_Explanation_FuelConsumption>Fuel consumption per platform</WTH_Explanation_FuelConsumption>
	<WTH_Explanation_TotalFuel>Total fuel</WTH_Explanation_TotalFuel>
	<WTH_Explanation_DaysOfFuel>Days of fuel</WTH_Explanation_DaysOfFuel>
	<WTH_Explanation_NotEnoughPlatforms>You don't have enough portable mechanoid platforms for the amount of mechanoids you selected. You should bring one for each mechanoid.</WTH_Explanation_NotEnoughPlatforms>
	<WTH_ExtraInfoKey_DaysOfFuel>Days of fuel (mechanoids)</WTH_ExtraInfoKey_DaysOfFuel>
	
	<WTH_Warning_NotEnoughPlatforms>Your caravan has not enough charging platforms to charge all mechanoids. You should bring one for each mechanoid, otherwise some mechanoids will run out of power very quickly.</WTH_Warning_NotEnoughPlatforms>
	<WTH_Warning_DaysOfFuel>You caravan has only {0} days worth of fuel for powering your mechanoids, and your mechanoids might run out of power quickly.</WTH_Warning_DaysOfFuel>
	<WTH_Message_CaravanOutOfFuel>{0} has run out of fuel.</WTH_Message_CaravanOutOfFuel>
	<WTH_Message_CannotDrop>This equipment is attached to the pawn, therefore you cannot drop it</WTH_Message_CannotDrop>
	<WTH_Message_EmergencySignalRaidInbound>The mechanoids near your base are already reacting to an earlier emergency signal and are on their way to your base. The operation therefore has no effect and the bill is cancelled.</WTH_Message_EmergencySignalRaidInbound>
	<WTH_Message_EmgergencySignalRaidCoolingDown>There aren't many mechanoids left in the surroundings, and the ones that are left have become suspicious. The operation therefore has no effect and the bill is cancelled.</WTH_Message_EmgergencySignalRaidCoolingDown>
	
	<WTH_Mount>Mount {0}</WTH_Mount>
	<WTH_Mount_Jobstring>Mounting {0}</WTH_Mount_Jobstring>
	
	<WTH_TextMote_MaintenanceFailed>Maintenance failed (success chance: {0})</WTH_TextMote_MaintenanceFailed>
	
</LanguageData>
