<Defs>
 <ConceptDef>
    <defName>WTH_Hacking</defName>
    <label>Mechanoid hacking</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <helpText>To hack mechanoids, go to the modifications section in the health tab of a downed mechanoid, and select the "Hack mechanoid targeting device" option. Your haulers will bring the mechanoid to the hacking facility (make sure you have one!), and a colonist with hacking assigned will start hacking the mechanoid. Don't forget to build mechanoid platforms so the mechanoid can be powered and repaired. Beware, hacking is dangerous!</helpText>
    <needsOpportunity>true</needsOpportunity>
  </ConceptDef>
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>WTH_Platform</defName>
    <label>Mechanoid platform</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <helpText>A mechanoid platform is a place where mechanoids are powered and repaired. The platform should be loaded with mechanoid parts and supplied with power. This way, mechanites inside the mechanoid are activated due to the large power supply and start repairing the mechanoid using the offered parts.</helpText>
    <needsOpportunity>true</needsOpportunity>
  </ConceptDef>
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>WTH_Modification</defName>
    <label>Mechanoid modification</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <helpText>In order to upgrade and modify mechanoids, you can craft upgrade modules at the mechanoid workshop. To install these modules, go to the modifications section in the health tab of a hacked mechanoid, and select the appropriate modification.</helpText>
    <needsOpportunity>true</needsOpportunity>
  </ConceptDef>
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>WTH_Caravanning</defName>
    <label>Caravanning with mechanoids</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <helpText>Mechanoids can also be used when caravanning. However, as always, they need power and maintenance. By bringing a portable mechanoid platform for each mechanoid in the caravan, and enough chemfuel, a steady power supply is ensured during the trip. If you want your mechanoids maintained during the trip, bring along some mechanoid parts, and a colonist capable of hacking. Mechanoids with repair modules installed will also repair themselves during the trip, and mechanoids with repair arms will repair any other mechanoid. If you don't want mechanoids to be repaired, go to their health tab, and set medical care to none.</helpText>
    <needsOpportunity>true</needsOpportunity>
  </ConceptDef>
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>WTH_Maintenance</defName>
    <label>Mechanoid maintenance</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <helpText>Hacking is a delicate business. Therefore, hacked mechanoids require regular maintenance, for which mechanoid parts are needed. Colonists with hacking assigned will automatically maintain your mechanoids, provided that you have enough parts available. Poorly maintained mechanoids won't function as well as properly maintained ones. Totally neglecting maintenance can result in the hack failing, with catastrophic consequences.</helpText>
    <needsOpportunity>true</needsOpportunity>
  </ConceptDef>
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>WTH_Power</defName>
    <label>Keeping mechanoids powered</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <helpText>Unlike "wild" mechanoids, hacked ones cannot use their reactor, as using it would result in detection by the mechanoid hive. Therefore, they rely on internal backup batteries, which can be charged on mechanoid platforms. Portable charging platforms can be used to supply mechanoids with power during world trips. Finally, there exist ways of improving the battery capacity, or installing an alternate power supply using the mechanoid workshop.</helpText>
    <needsOpportunity>true</needsOpportunity>
  </ConceptDef>
  <!--Added in v0.19.6 -->
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>WTH_Concept_MechanoidParts</defName>
    <label>Getting mechanoid parts</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <helpText>It is very important to always have some mechanoid parts in store for repairing, and more importantly, maintaining your mechanoids. Disassembling mechanoids is the primary way to get parts, but you can also buy them from exotic goods traders, and outlander towns. A way to get more mechanoids to disassemble, is by performing the "induce emergency signal" operation on a downed non-hacked mechanoid. You need to research "attracting mechanoids" to be able to do this. </helpText>
    <needsOpportunity>true</needsOpportunity>
  </ConceptDef>
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>WTH_Concept_RogueAI</defName>
    <label>Rogue AI: developing a consciousness</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <helpText>To get the full potential out of a rogue AI, go through the following steps:
1. Gather hive data. With the right research done, you can tune the long range mineral scanner to scan for "mechanoid parts". It'll guide you to places where you can like find hive data. 
2. Build a hiveship hacking facility, and use it to hack a hive ship. Your rogue AI will use the knowledge gathered after hacking to develop a consciousness.</helpText>
    <needsOpportunity>true</needsOpportunity>
  </ConceptDef>
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>WTH_Concept_RogueAI_LevelUp</defName>
    <label>Rogue AI: levelling up</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <helpText>After your rogue AI has developed a consciousness, it's still a shadow of what it could be. Gather more hive data and feed it to your Rogue AI to level it up. As it levels up, it'll gain more abilities.
Hint: You can also gather hive data by hacking more hive ships, or you can extract human brain data from live humans as an alternative to hive data</helpText>
    <needsOpportunity>true</needsOpportunity>
  </ConceptDef>
  <ConceptDef>
    <defName>WTH_Concept_RogueAI_Mood</defName>
    <label>Rogue AI: Mood</label>
    <priority>50</priority>
    <helpText>Keep an eye out for the mood of your Rogue AI. You certainly don't want to get it mad! Providing it with mechanoid data or extracted human brain data improves its mood, while using abilities, damaging it, and leaving it without electricity decreases its mood.</helpText>
    <needsOpportunity>true</needsOpportunity>
  </ConceptDef>
</Defs>